const questions = [
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 6?",
    options: ["2", "1", "0", "3"],
    answer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 18?",
    options: ["3", "2", "1", "4"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 9?",
    options: ["1", "2", "0", "3"],
    answer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 12?",
    options: ["3", "1", "2", "0"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 10?",
    options: ["1", "2", "0", "3"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 05?",
    options: ["3", "1", "2", "0"],
    answer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 30?",
    options: ["1", "3", "2", "0"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 39?",
    options: ["2", "3", "4", "1"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 50?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "0"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 11?",
    options: ["1", "3", "2", "4"],
    answer: "2",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 1?",
    options: ["2", "1", "3", "4"],
    answer: "1",
  },
  {
    question: "How many digits are in the number 44?",
    options: ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
    answer: "2",
  },
];
  
const leftInstructions = {
    general:{
        heading:"Instruction",
        text:"Answer the question in the right panel.<br> Click on any option to choose your answer."
    },
    correct:{
        heading:"Correct!",
        text:"You have answered the question correctly"
    },
    wrong:{
        heading:"Uh oh!",
        text:"Your answer is not correct.<br> Please try again."
    }
}